It's worth it.
When you have nothing,
worthiness is not even worth
the dust on the scale.
Do you want to hear the story later?
Later,
the devil gave me a pair of scissors,
and I turned it into a wedding dress.
Ignore the latecomers and absentees.
Let's have a meeting.
I believe everyone has seen the news.
I won't introduce myself.
I guess none of you here
welcomes my arrival as an outsider.
But it doesn't matter.
Because I don't need any of you to change.
But you have to learn to accept.
Unless you choose to withdraw from the Dark Fairy Tale project.
Dark Fairy Tale
a key project to enter the luxury market.
In the subsequent work,
I hope everyone here takes it seriously.
First,
let me tell you
the design concept of Dark Fairy Tale.
Dark Fairy Tale Series...
Get up.
Dear,
that champagne last night
ruined my mascara.
What are you doing?
Don't you see I'm busy?
My God!
Why are you staring at me?
You scared me to death.
Your makeup is cakey.
Really?
Chief designer of women's wear,
Jiang Datong.
Calling someone by their full name is really rude.
My name is Jeneri.
Jiang...
Being late for a meeting and ignoring the speaker is not rude?
If it weren't for Young Master,
who would want to listen to
your lecture at night?
No one forces you to join the Dark Fairy Tale.
I'm afraid you'll design something strange
and ruin our company's reputation.
Let's continue.
The Dark Fairy Tale series
will use a subversive aesthetic perspective
to analyze the pure appearance of traditional culture.
We will use luxurious fabrics and darkness...
Oh my god.
You don't understand women at all.
Women are like crystals,
like princesses in fairy tales.
After experiencing darkness,
finally...
Get out.
You're yelling at me?
Even the chairman and the young master never yelled at me.
You're just the young master's token fiancée.
You...
How dare you yell at me!
Do you need Lu Xu to kick you out?
Humph!
I'm watching you.
What's wrong with you?
You look upset.
Come on, try this.
It was just air-freighted from Naples.
It's said to be this year's champion bean.
I've been busy with work lately.
I wanna come here to have a rest.
If you have something to do, just leave.
Well,
as long as I don't meet a difficult client like Lu Qianqian,
I'm not that busy.
Li.
Miss Lu.
You...
Why are you here suddenly?
I'll make you a cup of coffee.
Don't bother.
We're old friends.
Don't be so formal.
Have a seat.
Sun,
get Ms. Lu a glass of lemon water.
Okay.
I bought this for you.
This scent
suits you perfectly.
The latest Hermes bag
goes perfectly with your
will be a perfect match.
How did you know I was here?
Xiaorou told me.
She said you've been coming here often.
I thought
I'd come here to take a chance.
I didn't expect
to actually find you.
Xiaorou
is really thoughtful.
Well,
I heard about it from my colleagues.
If you don't need anything,
I'll go back to the company.
OK.
Xiaorou,
the Bvlgari Rotating bracelet on your wrist
is very beautiful.
Why are you looking at me?
Do I have a flower on my face?
Qianqian, you look different today.
Let me share with you
some private thoughts
of a married woman.
My brother-in-law has been
doing quite well lately.
So it's about this kind of thing.
You're not married yet,
so you don't understand.
This is
not a trivial matter.
After getting married,
love
gradually turns into family affection.
Especially after having children,
the passion
is as flat as boiled water.
In the past two years,
I've been the one to initiate it eight out of ten times.
He even dares to reject me.
But recently,
he's been acting differently.
He's been very passionate.
It's like
the time before we got married,
before I got pregnant.
Were you and Mr. Zhou not getting along well?
It's not like that.
It's just that recently,
when he comes back from business trips,
he's been very passionate.
Usually,
he's just so-so.
Sis,
why are you frowning?
Oh, nothing.
I just thought of my cheating ex-husband.
You've been divorced?
I never heard you mention it.
You've been abroad all the time.
Of course, you wouldn't know.
I got divorced because of my ex-husband's cheating.
Our married life
wasn't harmonious.
He was only passionate
when he came back from business trips.
Later, I read a book on psychology.
It said that men who have cheated
would feel guilty.
To cover up their affairs,
they would suddenly be very passionate towards their wives,
using this as a form of compensation.
Until...
You don't have to say anything.
No one thinks you're a mute.
I'm sorry.
I...
I'll go tidy up a bit.
This place is really unlucky.
Let's go somewhere else.
I'm hungry.
What's the name of that cello piece
the cello piece
you played today?
It sounds familiar.
Zhou Jian,
I'll teach you a song.
It's my favorite.
Do you love Lu Qianqian?
I...
I like you.
I know you like me, too.
I know you
as well as I know myself.
We both live in disguise.
We resort to all means for a dark future.
Zhou Jian,
do you love me?
As long as you love me,
I will be the happiest woman in the world.
Zhou Jian,
do you love me?
I should go back.
Are you scared?
Hello?
What's up?
Mr. Zhou,
the proposal for limited edition of Dark Fairy Tale
was rejected by the board.
Rejected?
Wasn't it approved before?
I don't know.
And Mr. Zhuang also voted against it.
Answer the phone.
[You must be curious now.]
[Let me tell you]
[why the company rejected your proposal.]
You did this?
Why?
I'm happy to see you upset.
Limited release is the key strategy
to quickly transform the company.
Do you understand?
So what?
So your mischief must have limits.
Mischief?
Zhou Jian,
what do you want to do
after the rapid transformation?
Go public?
You want to take Golden Thread public so soon.
Is it for the company
or
for yourself?
You've used up all your luck
to marry into the Lu family.
Some things
are not for someone like you.
A second marriage son-in-law.
I'm telling you,
no matter how much my sister likes you,
you'll always be a dog of the Lu family.
Shut up!
Don't talk to me like that.
Do you hear me?
You can't talk to me like this.
Why are you here?
Uncle.
Mumu.
You've grown taller.
Do you miss me?
Yes.
Did you bring toys?
Of course.
I brought your favorite toy.
Come here.
Let me hold you.
You've grown heavier.
Sis,
this is my home too, isn't it?
Yan,
prepare a room for me.
Starting today,
I'm moving back to the Lu family mansion.
Mr. Zhuang,
I didn't expect you and the other shareholders
to reject Zhou Jian's proposal together.
Isn't it more in your interest
Release Dark Fairy Tale limitedly to open the market.
After all, Golden Thread is surnamed Lu, not Zhuang.
I'm just going with the flow.
Ah,
your chess skills are truly becoming unpredictable.
Mr. Liu, you're too kind.
If you hadn't gone easy on me,
how could I have won?
I gave it my all this time.
Especially this move.
It's perfectly balanced.
Ingenious.
I lost by five and a half points.
I'm completely convinced.